Becca: Hi, Dave.
Dave: Hi, Becca. Hi, Barry!
So nice to see you both again!
Becca: What a cute restaurant. I really like it.
And look at all the dogs.
Dave: I know, right!
It has good food, too…for people and for dogs!
Becca: Mmm. Sit, Barry. Good boy.
Uh, where’s Dolly?
Dave: She isn’t here.
Uh, Becca, I need to tell you something.
Dolly isn’t my dog. She’s my friend’s dog.
I sometimes help and take her for a walk.
Becca: You don’t have a dog?
Dave: No. Uh…I don’t like dogs very much.
And my apartment’s so small.
I’m so sorry. I know you love dogs.
Becca: Phew! Don’t worry!
Barry isn’t my dog either! He’s my sister’s dog.
I like dogs, but…in fact…I have two cats.
How do you feel about cats?
Dave: I love cats – in fact, I prefer cats to dogs!
Let’s sit down and order lunch.
Becca: Great!
So, what’s good here?
Dave: The spaghetti carbonara is fantastic –
and so is the homemade chocolate ice cream!
Becca: Yum! All for me this time!